<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Cairo</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">The city of a 1000 minarets</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Cairo</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="nav_item_home">Welcome to Cairo</string>
    <string name="nav_item_attractions">Top Attractions</string>
    <string name="nav_item_mosques">Most Beautiful Mosques</string>
    <string name="nav_item_parks">Parks and Gardens</string>
    <string name="nav_item_streets">Coolest Streets</string>

    <string name="main_activity_title">Cairo</string>

    <string name="home_fragment_details_1">Cairo is chaos at its most magnificent, infuriating and beautiful. From above, the distorted roar of the muezzins\' call to prayer echoes out from duelling minarets. Below, car horns bellow tuneless symphonies amid avenues of faded 19th-century grandeur while donkey carts rattle down dusty lanes lined with colossal Fatimid and Mamluk monuments.</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_details_2">This mega-city\'s constant buzz and noise is a product of its 22-or-so million inhabitants simultaneously crushing Cairo\'s infrastructure under their collective weight and lifting its spirits up with their exceptional humour. Your nerves will jangle, your snot will run black from the smog and touts will hound you at every turn, but it\'s a small price to pay to tap into the energy of the place Egyptians call Umm Ad Dunya – the Mother of the World.</string>
    <string name="home_fragment_details_3">Blow your nose, crack a joke and look through the dirt to see the city\'s true colours. If you love Cairo, it will definitely love you back.</string>
    <string name="testHardCoded">tesdfstt</string>
    <string name="street_title_Muizz">Muizz Street</string>
    <string name="street_desc_muizz">Muizz Street should totally be on the top of your list when visiting Cairo. Named after the fourth Fatimid Caliph Al-Mu’izz li-Deen Illah, Muizz Street is considered to be one of the oldest streets in Cairo and is one of the most vibrant and historic spots in the city. It extends from Bab A-Futuh (one of three remaining gates in the walls of Old Cairo) to Bab Zuweila, where you’ll find several markets in Al-Azhar Street and the Ghuriya Complex and the area around it. Here, there are plenty of stalls to buy souvenirs and antiques from. The whole area is rich with dozens of historic buildings from different eras including the Tulunid, Fatimid and Mamluk eras. According to a United Nation’s study, the street contains the largest gathering of medieval architectural treasures in the Islamic world.</string>
    <string name="street_hours_muizz">Daily: 24 hours</string>
    <string name="street_dir_muizz"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.050931,31.261575]]></string>
    <string name="street_title_saliba">Saliba Street</string>
    <string name="street_desc_saliba">Saliba (Cross) Street is another significant historic spot that dates back to the Middle Ages’ Cairo with numerous examples of great architecture from the Islamic period. The area, which now can be considered as an open-air museum, was once a residence to the state’s most important men — mostly from 1312 until 1517. Extending from the Citadel to the Ibn Tulun, and Sayyida Zeinab Mosque, the area has an abundance of Islamic monuments including mosques, schools, kuttab (an Islamic primary school mostly connected to the mosque), shrines and others.</string>
    <string name="street_open_saliba">Daily: 24 hours</string>
    <string name="street_loc_saliba"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.030432,31.251241]]></string>
    <string name="street_title_talaat">Talaat Harb Street</string>
    <string name="street_desc_talaat">Named after Talaat Pasha Harb, a famous Egyptian economist, the street was once a center for many social activities among the elites in Cairo. Now, it is considered as one of the most active streets in the city. It is located in the heart of Cairo’s European-ized area, Wust El-Balad (downtown). While strolling the street, you’ll be fascinated with the elegant historic buildings and the artistic atmosphere. You’ve got to try taking a walk there late at night.</string>
    <string name="street_open_talaat">Daily: 24 hours</string>
    <string name="street_loc_talaat"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.048963,31.239492]]></string>
    <string name="street_title_qasr">Qasr El Nil Street</string>
    <string name="street_desc_qasr">One of the biggest streets in Wust El-Balad and a home to several stores, nightlife spots, and important historic landmarks in Cairo is Qasr El Nil Street. It starts from Abdeen Square, passing by Bab El-Louq Market, American University downtown, Tahrir Square and the Egyptian Museum until it crosses the Nile through Qasr El Nil Bridge and then reaches Gezira Island. The important landmarks located here include Abdeen Palace (a historic royal residence), Egyptian Museum, Mogamma El Tahrir, Cairo Opera House and Museum Of Modern Egyptian Art.</string>
    <string name="street_open_qasr">Daily: 24 hours</string>
    <string name="street_loc_qasr"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.043747,31.229464]]></string>
    <string name="attract_title_pyramid">Pyramids of Giza</string>
    <string name="attract_pyramid_desc">The last remaining wonder of the ancient world; for nearly 4000 years, the extraordinary shape, impeccable geometry and sheer bulk of the Giza Pyramids have invited the obvious questions: ‘How were we built, and why?’. Centuries of research have given us parts of the answer. Built as massive tombs on the orders of the pharaohs, they were constructed by teams of workers tens-of-thousands strong. Today they stand as an awe-inspiring tribute to the might, organisation and achievements of ancient Egypt.</string>
    <string name="attract_pyramid_open">Daily: 8:00 am - 4:00 pm</string>
    <string name="attract_pyramid_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=29.979235,31.134202]]></string>
    <string name="attract_egymus_title">Egyptian Museum</string>
    <string name="attract_egymus_desc">One of the world’s most important collections of ancient artefacts, the Egyptian Museum takes pride of place in Downtown Cairo, on the north side of Midan Tahrir. Inside the great domed, oddly pinkish building, the glittering treasures of Tutankhamun and other great pharaohs lie alongside the grave goods, mummies, jewellery, eating bowls and toys of Egyptians whose names are lost to history.</string>
    <string name="attract_egymus_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 7:00 pm</string>
    <string name="attract_egymus_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.047847,31.233649]]></string>
    <string name="attract_islamicart_title">Museum of Islamic Art</string>
    <string name="attract_islamicart_desc">This museum, on the edge of Islamic Cairo, holds one of the world’s finest collections of Islamic art and is Egypt\'s (and one of the entire Middle East\'s) most beautifully curated museums. What’s on display is only a sliver of the 80,000 objects the museum owns, but the selected items are stunning. The museum was heavily damaged in January 2014 in a car-bomb attack on nearby police headquarters but after extensive renovations was finally reopened in early 2017.</string>
    <string name="attract_islamicart_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 5:00 pm</string>
    <string name="attract_islamicart_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.044362,31.252368]]></string>
    <string name="attract_azhar_title">Al Azhar Mosque</string>
    <string name="attract_azhar_desc">Founded in AD 970 as the centrepiece of the newly created Fatimid city, Al Azhar is one of Cairo’s earlier mosques, and its sheikh is considered the highest theological authority for Egyptian Muslims. The building is a harmonious blend of architectural styles, the result of numerous enlargements over more than 1000 years. The tomb chamber, located through a doorway on the left just inside the entrance, has a beautiful mihrab (a niche indicating the direction of Mecca) and should not be missed.</string>
    <string name="attract_azhar_open">Daily: 24 hours</string>
    <string name="attract_azhar_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.045688,31.262685]]></string>
    <string name="attract_khan_title">Khan Al Khalili</string>
    <string name="attract_khan_desc">The skinny lanes of Khan Al Khalili are basically a medieval-style mall. This agglomeration of shops – many arranged around small courtyards – stocks everything from soap powder to semiprecious stones, not to mention tacky toy camels and alabaster pyramids. Most shops and stalls open from around 9am to well after sundown (except Friday morning and Sunday), although plenty of the souvenir vendors are open as long as there are customers, even on Sunday.</string>
    <string name="attract_khan_open">Daily: 24 hours</string>
    <string name="attract_khan_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.047739,31.262254]]></string>
    <string name="attract_citadel_title">Citadel</string>
    <string name="attract_citadel_desc">Sprawling over a limestone spur on the city\'s eastern edge, the Citadel, started by Saladin in 1176 as a fortification against the Crusaders, was home to Egypt’s rulers for 700 years. Their legacy is a collection of three very different mosques, several palaces (housing some either underwhelming, or nearly-always closed museums) and a couple of terraces with superb Cairo views – on a clear day you\'ll see Giza\'s Pyramids poking up in the far distance.</string>
    <string name="attract_citadel_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 5:00 pm</string>
    <string name="attract_citadel_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.029860,31.261105]]></string>
    <string name="attract_hussein_title">Mosque of Sayyidna Al Hussein</string>
    <string name="attract_hussein_desc">One of the most sacred Islamic sites in Egypt, this mosque is the reputed burial place of the head of Hussein, the grandson of Prophet Mohammed. Most of the building dates from about 1870, except for the beautiful 14th-century stucco panels on the minaret. The modern metal sculptures in front are elegant Teflon canopies that expand to cover worshippers during Friday prayers. This is one of the few mosques where non-Muslims can\'t enter.</string>
    <string name="attract_hussein_open">Daily: 10:00 am - 10:00 pm</string>
    <string name="attract_hussein_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.047819,31.263169]]></string>
    <string name="attract_tower_title">Cairo Tower</string>
    <string name="attract_tower_desc">This 187m-high tower is the city’s most famous landmark after the Pyramids. Built in 1961, the structure, which resembles a stylised lotus plant with its latticework casing, was a thumb to the nose at the Americans, who had given Nasser the money used for its construction to buy US arms. The 360-degree views across the city from the top are clearest in the late morning, after the haze burns off, or late afternoon when you can often spy the Pyramids.</string>
    <string name="attract_tower_open">Daily: 8:00 am - midnight, to 1am summer</string>
    <string name="attract_tower_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.045915,31.224290]]></string>
    <string name="mosq_ali_title">MOSQUE OF MUHAMMED ALI</string>
    <string name="mosq_ali_desc">With a distinguished exterior and interior, the Mosque of Muhammed Ali is also known as the Alabaster Mosque. It is one of Egypt’s top tourist attractions. The mosque is situated on the Summit of Saladin Citadel, and has minarets measuring 270 feet in height–way above average! Tourists can view almost all of Cairo from above, including the Giza Plateau. The mosque was built between 1830 and 1957 by prominent architect Yussuf Bushnaq, and was commissioned by Muhammed Ali Pasha, erstwhile ruler of Egypt.</string>
    <string name="mosq_ali_open">Daily: 8:00 am - 5:00 pm</string>
    <string name="mosq_ali_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.0287015,31.259910600000012]]></string>
    <string name="mosq_as_title">MOSQUE OF AMR IBN AL-AS</string>
    <string name="mosq_as_desc">This is a particularly historically significant site, in that it was the first mosque to be built in Africa (641-642 CE). The mosque was home to General Amr Ibn Al-As’s tent, the commander of the Muslim army back then. It also holds the tomb of his son, Abd Allah Ibn Amr Ibn Al-As. The mosque was the first real university in the entire world, a center for learning and teaching, although it no longer serves this purpose. The site has been expanded and reconstructed over the years.</string>
    <string name="mosq_as_open">Daily: 8:00 am - 5:00 pm</string>
    <string name="mosq_as_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.0101215,5.2331368]]></string>
    <string name="mosq_tulun_title">MOSQUE OF IBN TULUN</string>
    <string name="mosq_tulun_desc">In the heart of Cairo lies the oldest and largest mosque in the city, the Mosque of Ibn Tulun. It is the oldest mosque to exist in its original form, and is also the largest in terms of land. It was constructed in 879 CE, commissioned by Ahmad ibn Tulun, Egypt’s governor at the time. The historical landmark is built on Gebel Yashkur, allowing visitors to take worthy shots of Cairo from its famous staircase minaret.</string>
    <string name="mosq_tulun_open">Daily: 5:00 am - 10:00 pm</string>
    <string name="mosq_tulun_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.02869100000001,31.249394100000018]]></string>
    <string name="mosq_hassan_title">MOSQUE-MADRASSA OF SULTAN HASSAN</string>
    <string name="mosq_hassan_desc">Considered one of the largest mosques in the world, the Mosque-Madrassa of Sultan Hassan is an historical and architectural landmark not to be missed. It was built during the Mamluk Islamic era (14th century) by Sultan Hassan, famous for his lavish spending. The landmark acted as a Madrassa (school) too, beside being a site of worship. There are teaching areas in the inner courtyard for the four main schools of Sunni Islamic theology: Hanafi, Malaki, Hanbali, and Shafi’i.</string>
    <string name="mosq_hassan_open">Daily: 8:00 am - 5:00 pm</string>
    <string name="mosq_hassan_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.0322791,31.256170399999974]]></string>
    <string name="mosq_rifa_title">AL-RIFA’I MOSQUE</string>
    <string name="mosq_rifa_desc">Right next to Sultan Hassan Mosque lies the beautiful Al-Rifa’i Mosque. It was built over 40 years, between 1869 and 1912, by the famous Egyptian engineer Hussein Fahmy Pasha. The mosque was commissioned by Khushyar Hanim, mother of Khedive Ismail Pasha, to expand the preexisting shrine of Islamic sanit Ahmed Al-Rifa’i. The mosque is home to Al-Rifa’i’s tomb, as well as many royal family members. Prayer takes place inside the mosque, despite the fact that it is against Islamic rules to pray in a mosque with tombs.</string>
    <string name="mosq_rifa_open">Daily: 8:00 am - 5:00 pm</string>
    <string name="mosq_rifa_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.0327091,31.257002899999975]]></string>
    <string name="mosq_hakim_title">AL-HAKIM BI-AMR ALLAH MOSQUE</string>
    <string name="mosq_hakim_desc">Known for its unique minarets, Al-Hakim bi-Amr Allah Mosque is the second major Fatimid mosque in Cairo. It was built between 990 and 1012 by Caliph Aziz, and completed by his son Al-Hakim bi-Amr Allah. The mosque was influenced by the famous Ibn Tulun Mosque, which is obvious in the arches supporting the arcades of the sanctuary, as well as the courtyard. The religious site is a peaceful place visited by both tourists and locals.</string>
    <string name="mosq_hakim_open">Daily: 8:00 am - 5:00 pm</string>
    <string name="mosq_hakim_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.0545766,31.264198999999962]]></string>
    <string name="mosq_azhar_title">AL-AZHAR MOSQUE</string>
    <string name="mosq_azhar_desc">Built in 970 CE, Al-Azhar’s sheikh is considered the highest theological authority among Egyptian Muslims. The building has seen extensive enlargements over its 1000-year history, and is a harmonious blend of architectural styles. The mosque has three minarets from the 14th, 15th and 16th centuries. The central courtyard is the oldest part. The building also hosts the world’s second-oldest university, from 988 CE, with its large modern campus being the most prestigious place to study Sunni theology.</string>
    <string name="mosq_azhar_open">Daily: 8:00 am - 4:00 pm</string>
    <string name="mosq_azhar_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.045688,31.2626851]]></string>
    <string name="mosq_qala_title">QALAWUN COMPLEX</string>
    <string name="mosq_qala_desc">Built by Sultan Al-Nasir Muhammad Ibn Qalawun in the 1280s, the complex includes a school, a hospital and a mausoleum. The complex was built in 13 months, which is a relatively short time considering its structure and the scope of the total complex. Its timeless design is considered the second most beautiful mausoleum, after the Taj Mahal in India.</string>
    <string name="mosq_qala_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 5:00 pm</string>
    <string name="mosq_qala_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.04939919999999,31.260961700000053]]></string>
    <string name="mosq_aqsun_title">AQSUNQUR MOSQUE</string>
    <string name="mosq_aqsun_desc">Dating from the 14th century, the Aqsunqur Mosque stands proudly in Cairo. Reflecting a clear Ottoman style, complete with typical Iznik tiles in the shape of cypress trees and tulips in vases, the mosque also contains the mausoleums of its founder, Shams El-Din Aqsunqur, and his numerous sons. The mosque is referred to as the “Blue Mosque” due to its blue and green tiles, which were added by Prince Ibrahim Agha Al-Mustahfizan between 1652 and ’54, during the Ottoman rule.</string>
    <string name="mosq_aqsun_open">Daily: 8:00 am - 5:00 pm</string>
    <string name="mosq_aqsun_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.0362363,31.2602223]]></string>
    <string name="mosq_naser_title">AL-NASSER MOHAMMED MOSQUE</string>
    <string name="mosq_naser_desc">Another mosque built by Sultan Al-Nasser Mohammed Ibn Qalawun in 1318, and renovated in 1334. It is a historical landmark as it lies inside the Citadel, across the street from the courtyard access to the Mosque of Muhammed Ali. It is where the sultans of Cairo used to perform their Friday prayers in its courtyard center. Despite the fact the the mosque is beautifully decorated inside, it has little-to-no decoration on the exterior.</string>
    <string name="mosq_naser_open">Daily: 8:00 am - 5:00 pm</string>
    <string name="mosq_naser_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.0290618,31.2609377]]></string>
    <string name="park_azhar_title">Al-Azhar Park</string>
    <string name="park_azhar_desc">Al-Azhar Park is one of Cairo’s largest parks as it covers a space of 80 acres. The space, originally a garbage dump, took seven years to be transformed to one of the most beautiful parks in Cairo. It opened to the public in 2005 and is located in the heart of historical Cairo, where the Citadel and Al Sultan Hassan Mosque surround it. Its position over a hill gives its visitors a magnificent view of Cairo. The green park has several fountains and restaurants where visitors can enjoy the natural beauty and the breathtaking views of Cairo.</string>
    <string name="park_azhar_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 10:00 pm</string>
    <string name="park_azhar_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.040632,31.264733]]></string>
    <string name="park_family_title">Family Park</string>
    <string name="park_family_desc">The Family Park is one of Cairo’s newest parks. Located on the Suez Road in New Cairo, the park offers many ways to enjoy the beauty of nature as well as amuse children. Activities inside the park can be categorized into two groups: educational and entertaining. An educational center has buildings that look like Bibliotheca Alexandria, the Giza Zoo, and the Martial Museum; all to give knowledge to children. There are also several theaters where kids can perform to the park’s visitors. In addition, the park displays various infotainment movies in its 3D cinema. On the entertainment side, the park has its own mini zoo and safari plaza where kids can see ostriches, ducks, deer, and other animals as well as explore different types of plants. A train takes visitors on a tour around the park and through a lighthouse where riders can see panoramic views of the park.</string>
    <string name="park_family_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 10:00 pm</string>
    <string name="park_family_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.080482,31.502140]]></string>
    <string name="park_inter_title">International Park</string>
    <string name="park_inter_desc">This park has International in its name because some of its flowers, trees, and animals originate from different countries around the world. One of its entrances has flags of the countries that are represented in the garden. The International Park offers a train ride where visitors can explore its different parts within 15 minutes. There is also a theatre inside the park as well as a mini zoo whose museum contains some mummified bodies and skeletons of animals with a small board of information for each.</string>
    <string name="park_inter_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 5:00 pm</string>
    <string name="park_inter_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.049414,31.336508]]></string>
    <string name="park_hor_title">Al Horreya Garden</string>
    <string name="park_hor_desc">Located in Zamalek across from Cairo Opera House and Al Andalus Garden, the Al Horreya Garden is known for its unique eleven statues of very important figures who had significant impact and positive change in their countries. Statues at Al Horreya, which means freedom, include Ahmed Shawky, the Prince of Poets, Talaat Harb Basha, a great Egyptian economist, and Hafez Ibrahim, the poet of the Nile. Others include some great people from Mexico, Ecuador, Venezuela, and other Latin-American countries. Most of these statues were gifts to Egypt from the countries they represent. Through the red-bricked pathway across its different parts, palm trees and fresh-green grass, Al Horreya offers a natural escape from Cairo’s noise and crowd.</string>
    <string name="park_hor_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 7:00 pm</string>
    <string name="park_hor_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.042082,31.225919]]></string>
    <string name="park_gro_title">Aquarium Grotto Garden</string>
    <string name="park_gro_desc">The Aquarium Grotto Garden—also called El Gabalaya Garden after the name of the street where it is located—was built in 1867 by Khedive Ismail, the viceroy of Egypt and Sudan. Unique for its architectural beauty, the garden’s formations are made of clay to look like fish gills. The Aquarium Grotto Garden has many underground grottoes that used to host various unique types of fish from the Nile and other places. Although the number of fish has decreased and some of the grottoes lie empty, the garden still hosts some rare fish that are worth watching. Besides the fish, a wide collection of various types of trees and flowers call the Aquarium Grotto home as well. The garden has been featured in several movies as a romantic spot since 1956.</string>
    <string name="park_gro_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 4:30 pm</string>
    <string name="park_gro_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.056570,31.218614]]></string>
    <string name="park_gez_title">Gezira Island</string>
    <string name="park_gez_desc">Located in the Nile in Central Cairo, three bridges connect Gezira Island across the river. The island was first called “Garden of Plants” because it had a unique variety of plants from all over the world. The northern part—known as Zamalek—is one of Cairo’s most-affluent districts and one of the most-appealing attractions to tourists as well as Egyptians. Besides the natural beauty and the green areas on the island, there are a lot of places to visit like the Cairo Tower, the Cairo Opera House, and the Gezira Sporting Club. It also headquarters many embassies and businesses, the best hotels, and the finest schools, which is why the island is a very attractive place to visit in Cairo.</string>
    <string name="park_gez_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 10:00 pm</string>
    <string name="park_gez_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.060942,31.219709]]></string>
    <string name="park_and_title">Al-Andalus Garden</string>
    <string name="park_and_desc">Formally known as El Tahrir Garden, Al-Andalus is located at the end of Zamalek between the Qasr El Nil and the 6 October bridges. Built by Zulfaqar Basha in 1935, who originally designed it to be part of the royal mansion of Khedive Ismail, the Garden is unique for the Andalusian-architectural style. This can be seen in the design of the entrance as well as the Andalusian-styled arches. Statues include those of some Pharaohs, lions, and one of Ahmed Shawky, the “Prince of Poets”. The park also hosts various types of palm trees and the vine-covered pergolas. A walk through nature with a breathtaking Nile view, attractive natural beauty, and unique-architectural art, Al-Andalus Garden is great escape to enjoy a mixture of distinct cultures, human civilizations, and nature.</string>
    <string name="park_and_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 10:00 pm</string>
    <string name="park_and_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.045573,31.225896]]></string>
    <string name="park_jap_title">Japanese Garden</string>
    <string name="park_jap_desc">The Japanese Garden, located in Helwan, Cairo, was built in 1917 by the Egyptian architect Zulfaqar Basha to represent cultures of the East. Full of fish ponds, hills, canals, and diverse trees the garden is most famous for its unique statues. For example, more than 30 Buddha statues—including the famous seated Buddha statue over a Lotus flower—and three statues of elephants adorn the garden. A lake there contains a statue of the three wise monkeys and their proverbial principle: “See no evil, Hear no evil, Speak no evil”. In front of that lake stands another statue of a master sitting with 48 students to teach them Buddhism. Along with the statues, the garden also has a promenade flanked by lanterns, a tall pagoda—a Buddhist temple—and a gazebo where some bands perform.</string>
    <string name="park_jap_open">Daily: 10:00 am - 4:00 pm</string>
    <string name="park_jap_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=29.848854,31.340224]]></string>
    <string name="park_orm_title">Orman Garden</string>
    <string name="park_orm_desc">Orman Garden, one of Egypt’s most famous botanical gardens, was built during Khedive Ismail’s rule in 1875. He ordered French architects to build it as he wanted to provide different types of fruits and vegetables to the royal palace. Brought from different parts of the world including Europe and China, this garden used to host more than 150 types of flowers and over 500 kinds of rare plants. This makes the garden a perfect host for its famous yearly spring festival which attracts visitors during March and April. Covering around 28 acres, the garden also has a pond with a wooden bridge that stretches over it. The Orman, Turkish for the forest, is located west of the Nile River, east of the Cairo University, and next to the Giza Zoo.</string>
    <string name="park_orm_open">Daily: 9:00 am - 4:00 pm</string>
    <string name="park_orm_loc"><![CDATA[https://www.google.com/maps/dir/?api=1&destination=30.029038,31.212977]]></string>


</resources>
